Now then, let's continue with the meat.
Let's grill!
I'm so glad you guys are going to eat it.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you cook it too hot, the mustard will burn.
But it was fun to see it burn and fly in my face!
Hot!
I've never had that before.
Looks so good!
I love it!
That's so good!
The trick is to do it on low heat.
If you get it right, the mustard will dance.
Oh, yeah?
What does that mean?
It's the heat.
It crackles.
It bounces.
It's really convenient, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's great that you can put the meat inside the pack.
It's the last thing you need to do because you can't drown the meat in the fire.
When I'm camping, I'm in the countryside.
They sell meat from there.
That's for sure.
It's unique to the area.
There's a lot of selfies and brand-name pork nowadays.
So it's nice to have a local one.
It goes with pretty much any meat.
Versatile.
Sounds good.
Not like this.
No, it's not.
But it went surprisingly well, didn't it?
Surprisingly easy.
We're developing other flavors now.
What kind of flavors should we come up with?
I'm still working on it.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'll make a kind of salt sauce.
You could put fish fillets or something in it.
I'm already thinking about a second album.
Please don't call it an album.
Not just for campers, but for home too.
At home, too.
You didn't go through the whole kaori thing, did you?
I'm not there yet, but the sound is getting better.
It's happening so fast.
Soon.
Not only meat, but vegetables, too, if you eat them all.
It looks so delicious.
Like onions.
They have a unique sweetness, don't they?
Yes, it does.
I think only Tomo and I can see it.
We're dancing.
Dancing?
Oh, really?
That's amazing.
Yes, it is.
It's crackling.
Pretty mustard.
That's a big one.
Oh, my God.
I love the visual.
It's a big, big grain.
Yes, they are.
I can't wait to eat them.
I'm almost done.
I'm trying to take some of the spiciness out of this mustard so it's not so harsh.
I think it's good like this.
Let's eat this.
Let's eat it.
Now that it's ready, let's eat it.
Please eat it in no time.
Bon appétit!
It's really what I was baking earlier.
It's still morning.
It smells so good!
Bon appétit!
It tastes like this.
It's good right after you put it in.
Tasty?
Delicious.
I'm so happy.
Yes!
I didn't think mustard would work.
Mustard is fun.
It's got a nice texture.
I'm glad.
You know, you've got a lot of mustard on your plate, and I've got a lot of mustard on mine.
I'm going to have mustard sense in my least favorite places.
That's how much mustard I want to eat.
Delicious!
It's basically a sweet and spicy base.
Kids will enjoy it too.
Why is it so fruity?
Oh, it's in there.
The base sauce is not too rich.
It goes well with it.It's good.
It's delicious.
Beer.
It goes well with beer.
It's good.
Bon appétit.
I'm so happy.
Delicious!
Yum!
You can eat this kind of food indefinitely.
It's endless!
I really want to use this at the festival.
I'd like to ask you for this.
Can you put it in my room every day?
That's not what I want.
I want to serve this.
I want to serve it with home-grown meat.
Yes, domestic meat.
You know, I've been thinking about this ever since I had it before.
I've been thinking about this ever since I had it before, but this sauce also has a kind of miso-like taste to it.
When you mix them together like this...
It's like the taste of your mother's cooking, which is familiar to Japanese people.
It's very gentle.
That's why I want to serve it.
What should we do?
How do you serve it?
Dip it in and have them eat it.
You can sell them in packs.
This one.
If it's good, it's good.
It's good, isn't it?
The first thing that popped into my head was...
In this forest of meat, there was a huge, beautiful bucket in the center.
In the center of this forest of meat, there was a huge, beautiful bucket.
You put your meat in there, and you're not allowed to marinate it twice.
Oh, no!
It's a little bit too much, isn't it?
If you do it many times.
That's why I rejected it.
I did.
I'd like to think a little bit about what I'm going to do after I've done that.
I made rice burgers the other day.
I put meat with this on it.
And it was really good.
I knew that for a festival, you need one-hand
meat.
I think it's a good item.
Can we go to Rice Burger?
Not today?
No, the day of.
The day of?
Can we go today?
Can you go today?
I can go today.
I've got it right here.
Then I'll let you have a taste.
We're adding staff in the kitchen.
Do you have mayo?
Mayo.
This is gonna get a lot of mayo.
Mayo mayo.
Mayo mayo, mayo mayo, mayo mayo.
Do you have any Tabasco?
All of it.
What's this one called?
This one?
Wild pack.
Wild pack?
Yes, sir.
It comes in a pack.
Wild pack.
Where did you get it?
Asooba's, right?
I had it at my office.
In Shimokitazawa, 4th floor.
Shibayama-san's office?
Yes.
So, I did one thing wrong.
I ate the wrong way.
I noticed it today...
Mr. Asooba's frying technique made me realize...
I'm a person of character.
I'm already going full ten.
High heat?
I'm like, "If it smokes, it's good.
If it smokes, it tastes good.
I see.
Smoky. That's great! That's what they said.
We were all eating together.
Some of it's a little rare, some of it's a little...
Some parts were a little rare, some parts were a little burnt.
And that's what made it so delicious.
And as a result, while we were eating it
Bipong!
We got a call about a fire.
What?
That's what it sounds like.If you ask me...
Was it that much? Smoke?
No, there's no fire.
Let me just come in.
They just came in with a bang.
On the ceiling of my office.
On the ceiling of my office, the sprinkler system.
It's turning red.
Oh, yeah.
Fire extinguishers are reacting.
This thing reacted.
Go to the fire department.
We're not 100 meters from the fire station.
Fire station is less than 100 meters away.
They got here as soon as they could.
What were you doing?
I was cooking meat.
Which meat?
This one.
How can you cook meat like this?
The sauce was very savory.
It has nothing to do with the taste.
The more sauce, the more smoke.
Did the sauce do this?
I showed the fire department.
I showed it to the fire department.
Here.
Can you not make too big a deal out of this?
It's an important time.
I'm doing a negative promotion.
Please don't start a fire.
Open the windows.
Turn on the exhaust fans.
As long as it's open, it should be fine.
I'm fine.
You overcooked it.
There was a blur.
About three professional portions at a time.
Was it too much?
Let's all eat together at the office.
Let's be careful.
Here come the riceburgers!
Here they are!
The restaurant is amazing!
Please eat it!
Bon appétit!
I'm so happy!
This is amazing!
Looks amazing!
So much food!
There's cheese, too!
Lettuce!
Bon appétit!
So much food!
How do I eat it?
Bon appétit!
This is a very generous portion.
It's enough for one meal.
Delicious!
Mmm!
The rice tastes good, too.
The rice is good too!
Delicious!
It goes so well with the rice!
It's delicious!
Delicious!
You can change the flavor to your liking.
Yummy!
We have Tabasco and curry powder.
Mayumi puts Tabasco on it.
Mayumi likes spicy food.
Well, then... it'll definitely go well with it.
I'll have some Tabasco.
Okay.
That's good.
Mmm!
Okay, I'll go there.
What's it like? How much?
A little!
Can I have more if you like?
Let's try this much.
Bon appétit!
The strength of the mustard when mixed with the other stuff feels amazing, doesn't it?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Does it go with it?
Yes! Yes! It's good!
Is it good?
Yeah! Yeah!
It's so good from the first time you put it in your mouth.
Wow! I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
It's so good!
It's totally different from the real thing, isn't it?
The addition of Tabasco's acidity and spiciness
I feel like it changes the image of sweet and spicy
I feel like it's a lot more mature.
Wow! Delicious!
I dared not to make it too sharp at the beginningI'm daring you to start with no horns.
You can spice it up or corner it in the middle.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
It wraps up everything.
It's supposed to be really gutsy, but it's so gentle.
Hey!
It's like Korean gochujang, but with a sweet and spicy base.
You should definitely try it!
Curry.
It's so much fun to change the flavor!
It's fun to change it up!
Curry sounds good, too.
You could put Tabasco or something next to where you sell this, too.
You should put some Tabasco or something next to where you sell it.
That's for sure.
I think I'll just have it with whatever you like.
Oh, no!
Curry?
Curry? !
Oh, man!
Is it good curry?
Yes!
It's so good!
Mmm.
We didn't do it.
No, we haven't.
Let's do it.
Just a little bit?
You know, if we go too far...
Just a little bit.
It's too much control.
Yum!
Curry powder would probably be good, too.
Curry powder, please.
Is it so good it's funny?
It's so good it's funny.
It's so good!
Oh, my God.
Curry powder is a good idea.
Curry goes so well with beer.
I'm so happy.
I'm sure it's good.
It's delicious!
I'm so happy.
Can I have some curry?
Yes, please.
Curry's amazing. It adds so much depth.
I'll have some too.
I can hold it all up with one hand.
The possibilities are endless.
Curry is amazing. I can taste the aftertaste.
It's so sweet!
It's so good!
Excuse me, what's that over there?
What's that over there?
Oh, no!
It looks like paprika!
I didn't think of curry, but...
It fits! It goes so well with curry!
If you think about it, meat, tomatoes, and cheese go well with curry.
I'm so happy!
Thank you for watching!
Yeah...
That's not enough.
Bon appétit.
Not dry enough?
Looks delicious.
Yum.
Here's the wild pack and the horinisheu.
Bon appétit!
Don't fight with each other.
I like the feeling of going along with it.
to get along with
with anyone.
the green onions are good again
Delicious
Yum
Good.
It's good.
I see. It's good.
I end up looking for mustard all the time.
It's over before you know it.
Right?
Yeah, it's good.
A bowl of rice is good, too.
It goes really well with vegetables, too.
It's totally good.
Delicious!
It's like this, but with a totally different variation.
We went to a curry shop, didn't we?
I went to a curry shop.
I'm sure it's good if we go to a curry shop.
This is really good!
It's beyond my mom's taste.It's beyond my mother's taste.
You don't often exceed your mother's taste.
No, it doesn't.
This is so good.
I'm glad you like it.
You should try it.
I want everyone to try it.
I want you to try it.
It's delicious!
Let's do this generation after generation.
Thank you very much.
Let's talk again about what form to serve it in.
In the forest of meat, what will you serve in the form of a deer?
We have two days, so after we cook together a few times...
I think you'll want to eat it a few more times.
In the forest of meat
I will make a deer table for one family per day.
I'm going to stay with the family for 90 minutes.
Even my friends.
I'll serve them for 90 minutes.
It's going to be a little expensive.
But I know how to run it, and I'll do it.
If you give me a price that includes the management fee.
I'll do it.
So I'm going to take the liberty of arranging this sauce in various ways.
I see. Sounds fun.
I'm going to make you eat it as much as you want.
I'd like that very much.
Mr. Shikano said that the road to food is a thorny one.
The scandal.
Ono-chan is going down that road.
I was just saying that.
I said that earlier, didn't I?
You've been king.
Personally, I don't care anymore.
Why?
Because it's delicious.
What do you think?
It's a project where we're trying to get you to eat it.
I think it's great!
Please go ahead and do it, everyone.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to start from there.
So that you can get to know us better.
From here to Mild Park.
Scandal from Mild Park.
We've been doing all kinds of activities.
We've interacted with the core from many different avenues.
This is now a whole new path.
Like, "Hey, that girl who makes the riceburgers.
She's also in a band.
That's totally possible.
Asakawa-san... listening to this situation objectively...
The way you're into this sauce...
It's 4-1.
Is that right?
Are you okay with that?
I was 1-1.
Yes, you were.
It's 4-1.
I have a little bit of a fever.
We worked on it together.
So we're going to release it?
Absolutely.
We're looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I hope you enjoy the ajijichen.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes.